[
  {
    "id": 601,
    "question": "situación",
    "questionDetails": "La situación de la ciudad es agradable.",
    "answer": "situation",
    "answerDetails": "The situation of the town is pleasant."
  },
  {
    "id": 602,
    "question": "ropa",
    "questionDetails": "Las víctimas del terremoto necesitan comida, ropa y frazadas.",
    "answer": "clothing, wear, apparel",
    "answerDetails": "The earthquake victims are in need of food, clothing, and blankets."
  },
  {
    "id": 603,
    "question": "tierra",
    "questionDetails": "Mi familia había trabajado la tierra durante muchos años.",
    "answer": "land, ground, soil",
    "answerDetails": "My family had worked the land for many years."
  },
  {
    "id": 604,
    "question": "alto",
    "questionDetails": "Hay que tomar un ascensor especial para subir a lo alto del edificio.",
    "answer": "top, upper, height",
    "answerDetails": "One must take a special elevator to reach the top of the building."
  },
  {
    "id": 605,
    "question": "supuesto",
    "questionDetails": "Tu idea se basa en el supuesto erróneo de que la gente se comporta de forma racional.",
    "answer": "assumption",
    "answerDetails": "Your idea is based on the erroneous assumption that people behave rationally."
  },
  {
    "id": 606,
    "question": "libre",
    "questionDetails": "El holandés libre, el pulimento libre, y las flotas noruegas libres.",
    "answer": "free, available, spare",
    "answerDetails": "The Free Dutch, Free Polish, and Free Norwegian fleets."
  },
  {
    "id": 607,
    "question": "algunos",
    "questionDetails": "Algunos individuos pueden recuperarse sin necesitar medicamentos.",
    "answer": "some",
    "answerDetails": "Some individuals may recover on their own without medication."
  },
  {
    "id": 608,
    "question": "segura",
    "questionDetails": "No estaria tan segura.",
    "answer": "sure, safe, secure",
    "answerDetails": "Do not be so sure."
  },
  {
    "id": 609,
    "question": "necesitamos",
    "questionDetails": "Necesitamos su ayuda para solucionar un problema.",
    "answer": "we need",
    "answerDetails": "We need your help to solve an issue."
  },
  {
    "id": 610,
    "question": "sangre",
    "questionDetails": "Sangre por debajo de la puerta.",
    "answer": "blood",
    "answerDetails": "Blood under the door."
  },
  {
    "id": 611,
    "question": "habrá",
    "questionDetails": "Habrá un concierto en la plaza esta noche.",
    "answer": "there will be",
    "answerDetails": "There will be a concert in the plaza tonight."
  },
  {
    "id": 612,
    "question": "trata",
    "questionDetails": "Trata de insert arte.",
    "answer": "try",
    "answerDetails": "Try to insert yourself."
  },
  {
    "id": 613,
    "question": "frente",
    "questionDetails": "Rápidamente se volvió la cabeza para enfrentar el frente.",
    "answer": "front, against, brow",
    "answerDetails": "She quickly turned her head to face the front."
  },
  {
    "id": 614,
    "question": "cuarto",
    "questionDetails": "Que no podía hacer nada mejor que terminar cuarto.",
    "answer": "fourth, quarter",
    "answerDetails": "He could do no better than finish fourth."
  },
  {
    "id": 615,
    "question": "escuchar",
    "questionDetails": "Le dije una y otra vez, pero ella no quiso escuchar.",
    "answer": "listen, hear",
    "answerDetails": "I told her over and over again, but she wouldn’t listen."
  },
  {
    "id": 616,
    "question": "hermana",
    "questionDetails": "Y a ver a mi hermana.",
    "answer": "sister",
    "answerDetails": "And to see my sister."
  },
  {
    "id": 617,
    "question": "encanta",
    "questionDetails": "Me encanta esta gente.",
    "answer": "love, adore",
    "answerDetails": "I love this crowd."
  },
  {
    "id": 618,
    "question": "vio",
    "questionDetails": "Estoy segura de que me vio, pero fingió no darse cuenta.",
    "answer": "he saw, saw him, he watched",
    "answerDetails": "I’m sure he saw me, but pretended not to notice me."
  },
  {
    "id": 619,
    "question": "especial",
    "questionDetails": "Gracias por hacer de mi cumpleaños un día muy especial.",
    "answer": "special, particular",
    "answerDetails": "Thank you for making my birthday a very special Day."
  },
  {
    "id": 620,
    "question": "resto",
    "questionDetails": "Mi intención es comer un poco del pastel ahora y dejar el resto para esta noche.",
    "answer": "rest, remainder",
    "answerDetails": "I plan to eat some of the cake and leave the rest for tonight."
  },
  {
    "id": 621,
    "question": "principio",
    "questionDetails": "Es un hombre íntegro que jamás traicionó sus principios.",
    "answer": "principle, beginning, start",
    "answerDetails": "He is an upright man who has never betrayed his principles."
  },
  {
    "id": 622,
    "question": "media",
    "questionDetails": "De media, alrededor de 2, 000 personas asisten a esos mítines.",
    "answer": "average, half hour, mean",
    "answerDetails": "On average, about 2,000 people attend those meetings."
  },
  {
    "id": 623,
    "question": "amiga",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Claro que conozco a Lucy! ¡ Es una amiga de toda la vida!.",
    "answer": "pal",
    "answerDetails": "Of course I know Lucy! She’s one of my old pals!."
  },
  {
    "id": 624,
    "question": "verte",
    "questionDetails": "Pueden verte llegar a una milla.",
    "answer": "seeyou, see",
    "answerDetails": "They can seeyou coming from a mile away."
  },
  {
    "id": 625,
    "question": "puso",
    "answer": "Put"
  },
  {
    "id": 626,
    "question": "querido",
    "questionDetails": "Querido Tom: ¿Cómo están tus hijos?",
    "answer": "dear",
    "answerDetails": "Dear Tom, How are the children?"
  },
  {
    "id": 627,
    "question": "chicos",
    "questionDetails": "Y eso hablando de los chicos.",
    "answer": "boys",
    "answerDetails": "And that’s just the boys."
  },
  {
    "id": 628,
    "question": "recuerdo",
    "questionDetails": "No tengo ningún recuerdo de esa noche.",
    "answer": "recall, souvenir, remembrance",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t have any recall from that night."
  },
  {
    "id": 629,
    "question": "teníamos",
    "questionDetails": "Teníamos muchas alergias cuando éramos pequeños.",
    "answer": "we had",
    "answerDetails": "We had a lot of allergies when we were little."
  },
  {
    "id": 630,
    "question": "encuentro",
    "questionDetails": "Nuestro Agente Secreto en Berlín no acudió al encuentro acostumbrado.",
    "answer": "rendezvous",
    "answerDetails": "Our secret agent in Berlin missed the usual rendezvous."
  },
  {
    "id": 631,
    "question": "pensaba",
    "answer": "i was thinking"
  },
  {
    "id": 632,
    "question": "vea",
    "questionDetails": "Quiero que la gente lo vea.",
    "answer": "see, watch, look",
    "answerDetails": "I want people to see that."
  },
  {
    "id": 633,
    "question": "jefe",
    "questionDetails": "El jefe de la policía.",
    "answer": "chief",
    "answerDetails": "The chief of police."
  },
  {
    "id": 634,
    "question": "vete",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Vete, niño!.",
    "answer": "go away, get gone",
    "answerDetails": "Go away, kid!."
  },
  {
    "id": 635,
    "question": "cama",
    "questionDetails": "Estaba en la cama con la mafia.",
    "answer": "bed, bunk",
    "answerDetails": "He was in bed with the Mob."
  },
  {
    "id": 636,
    "question": "venido",
    "questionDetails": "Pude haber venido antes pero tu ayuno ayuda.",
    "answer": "come",
    "answerDetails": "I could have come earlier but your fast has helped."
  },
  {
    "id": 637,
    "question": "comprar",
    "questionDetails": "Comprar algo a Or para alguien.",
    "answer": "buy, shop",
    "answerDetails": "To buy somebody something, to buy something for somebody."
  },
  {
    "id": 638,
    "question": "pongo",
    "questionDetails": "Me siento a mi escritorio y pongo comas.",
    "answer": "put, wear",
    "answerDetails": "I sit at my desk and put commas in."
  },
  {
    "id": 639,
    "question": "siguiente",
    "questionDetails": "Las siguientes son frases gramaticalmente correctas.",
    "answer": "following",
    "answerDetails": "The following are both grammatically correct sentences."
  },
  {
    "id": 640,
    "question": "niña",
    "questionDetails": "¿Ya saben el sexo del bebé?-Es una niña.",
    "answer": "she",
    "answerDetails": "Have you found out the sex of the baby?-It’s a she."
  },
  {
    "id": 641,
    "question": "terminar",
    "questionDetails": "No sé cómo terminar esta relación.",
    "answer": "end, complete, conclude",
    "answerDetails": "I don’t know how to end this relationship."
  },
  {
    "id": 642,
    "question": "acabo",
    "questionDetails": "A veces comienzo a reírme cuando acabo y se asusta mi pareja.",
    "answer": "i am coming",
    "answerDetails": "Sometimes I start laughing when I am coming and my partner freaks out."
  },
  {
    "id": 643,
    "question": "hacia",
    "questionDetails": "Él era cálido y tierno hacia su.",
    "answer": "towards, around, at",
    "answerDetails": "He was warm and tender towards her."
  },
  {
    "id": 644,
    "question": "delante",
    "questionDetails": "Pero no me preocupa delante de ti.",
    "answer": "before",
    "answerDetails": "But before you worry me."
  },
  {
    "id": 645,
    "question": "hubo",
    "answer": "there were"
  },
  {
    "id": 646,
    "question": "uy",
    "questionDetails": "¡ Uy! ¿Pero qué haces tú aquí?",
    "answer": "whoa",
    "answerDetails": "Whoa! But what are you doing here?"
  },
  {
    "id": 647,
    "question": "vine",
    "answer": "Came"
  },
  {
    "id": 648,
    "question": "jamás",
    "questionDetails": "Su cuerpo jamás fue recuperado.",
    "answer": "never, ever",
    "answerDetails": "His body was never recovered."
  },
  {
    "id": 649,
    "question": "voz",
    "questionDetails": "Levantar/bajar la voz.",
    "answer": "voice, word",
    "answerDetails": "To raise/lower one’s voice."
  },
  {
    "id": 650,
    "question": "hicieron",
    "questionDetails": "Se nos robaron los pasaportes cuando estábamos de viaje.-¿Qué hicieron? ¿Como volvieron?",
    "answer": "did you do",
    "answerDetails": "Our passports were stolen while traveling.-What did you do? How did you get home?"
  },
  {
    "id": 651,
    "question": "detrás",
    "questionDetails": "La casa tiene un jardín grande detrás.",
    "answer": "back, behind, in tow",
    "answerDetails": "The house’s got a large garden at the back."
  },
  {
    "id": 652,
    "question": "venía",
    "questionDetails": "Sí, recuerdo a Sandra. Venía a mi oficina para citas muy frecuentemente.",
    "answer": "she came",
    "answerDetails": "Yes, I remember Sandra. She came to my office for appointments very frequently."
  },
  {
    "id": 653,
    "question": "pelo",
    "questionDetails": "Tienes que recogerte el pelo para trabajar en mi cocina.",
    "answer": "hair",
    "answerDetails": "You have to put your hair up to work in my kitchen."
  },
  {
    "id": 654,
    "question": "quedan",
    "questionDetails": "Quedan dos criaturas, mi señor.",
    "answer": "remain, left, are",
    "answerDetails": "Two creatures remain, my lord."
  },
  {
    "id": 655,
    "question": "dé",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces, dé me uno de éstos.",
    "answer": "give",
    "answerDetails": "Then give me one of these."
  },
  {
    "id": 656,
    "question": "derecho",
    "questionDetails": "No siempre ha permanecido en el lado derecho de la ley.",
    "answer": "right",
    "answerDetails": "He hasn’t always remained on the right side of the law."
  },
  {
    "id": 657,
    "question": "sorpresa",
    "questionDetails": "Te confiamos con el cuidado de Jason y sorpresa sorpresa, que hacer un desastre de la misma.",
    "answer": "surprise",
    "answerDetails": "We entrust you with Jason’s care and, surprise surprise, you make a mess of it."
  },
  {
    "id": 658,
    "question": "acabó",
    "questionDetails": "Seguiste dormida en mis brazos hasta que acabó el partido.",
    "answer": "ended, finished, ended up",
    "answerDetails": "You stayed asleep in my arms till the game ended."
  },
  {
    "id": 659,
    "question": "durante",
    "questionDetails": "Las mujeres deben evitar el alcohol durante el embarazo.",
    "answer": "during, over, for",
    "answerDetails": "Women should avoid alcohol during pregnancy."
  },
  {
    "id": 660,
    "question": "cuántos",
    "answer": "how many"
  },
  {
    "id": 661,
    "question": "realmente",
    "questionDetails": "Realmente, Marjorie, ¡ Salta a las conclusiones!.",
    "answer": "really, actually, truly",
    "answerDetails": "Really, Marjorie, you do jump to conclusions!."
  },
  {
    "id": 662,
    "question": "mensaje",
    "questionDetails": "Captó el mensaje y se mantuvo alejado.",
    "answer": "message",
    "answerDetails": "He got the message and stayed away."
  },
  {
    "id": 663,
    "question": "futuro",
    "questionDetails": "Había decidido que no había futuro en la pandilla.",
    "answer": "future",
    "answerDetails": "He’d decided that there was no future in the gang."
  },
  {
    "id": 664,
    "question": "don",
    "questionDetails": "Tener un don para las matemáticas.",
    "answer": "gift, mr, knack",
    "answerDetails": "To have a gift for mathematics."
  },
  {
    "id": 665,
    "question": "cuento",
    "questionDetails": "No me dormiré hasta que no me cuentes un cuento.",
    "answer": "story",
    "answerDetails": "I won’t go to sleep unless you tell me a story."
  },
  {
    "id": 666,
    "question": "música",
    "questionDetails": "Poner música a la letra.",
    "answer": "music",
    "answerDetails": "To set words to music."
  },
  {
    "id": 667,
    "question": "increíble",
    "questionDetails": "Un número increíble de personas registradas.",
    "answer": "amazing, incredible",
    "answerDetails": "An amazing number of people registered."
  },
  {
    "id": 668,
    "question": "hablo",
    "questionDetails": "Yo hablo su idioma, por así decirlo.",
    "answer": "speak, talk",
    "answerDetails": "I speak their language, you might say."
  },
  {
    "id": 669,
    "question": "personal",
    "questionDetails": "El personal de la oficina trabaja mucho.",
    "answer": "staff, personnel",
    "answerDetails": "The staff of the office works hard."
  },
  {
    "id": 670,
    "question": "vuelvo",
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "id": 671,
    "question": "perdido",
    "questionDetails": "Dar algo/a alguien por perdido (a).",
    "answer": "lost",
    "answerDetails": "To give something/somebody up for lost."
  },
  {
    "id": 672,
    "question": "loca",
    "questionDetails": "Ya sé que está loca de remate.",
    "answer": "crazy",
    "answerDetails": "I know you’re crazy auction."
  },
  {
    "id": 673,
    "question": "deje",
    "answer": "i left"
  },
  {
    "id": 674,
    "question": "novia",
    "questionDetails": "Tenía una novia y un amigo.",
    "answer": "sweetheart",
    "answerDetails": "I had a sweetheart and a friend."
  },
  {
    "id": 675,
    "question": "fuiste",
    "questionDetails": "La escuela fue interesante ayer. ¿Fuiste?",
    "answer": "did you go",
    "answerDetails": "School was interesting yesterday. Did you go?"
  },
  {
    "id": 676,
    "question": "clase",
    "questionDetails": "Basta ver la forma que tiene de sujetar el cigarro para darse cuenta de que tiene clase.",
    "answer": "class",
    "answerDetails": "Just by looking at the way she holds her cigarette, you can tell she’s got class."
  },
  {
    "id": 677,
    "question": "exactamente",
    "questionDetails": "¿Qué es exactamente lo que busca?",
    "answer": "exactly, precisely",
    "answerDetails": "What exactly are you looking for?"
  },
  {
    "id": 678,
    "question": "tuya",
    "questionDetails": "La responsabilidad no es nuestra sino tuya.",
    "answer": "thine",
    "answerDetails": "The responsibility is not ours but thine."
  },
  {
    "id": 679,
    "question": "mejores",
    "questionDetails": "Tengo algunos de los mejores doctores del mundo.",
    "answer": "best, finest, top",
    "answerDetails": "I have some of the best doctors in the world."
  },
  {
    "id": 680,
    "question": "chico",
    "questionDetails": "Yo era el chico nuevo en la oficina.",
    "answer": "boy",
    "answerDetails": "I was the new boy at the office."
  },
  {
    "id": 681,
    "question": "empieza",
    "questionDetails": "Entonces Laura Alza la mano. “Yo creo,” empieza a decir.",
    "answer": "she begins, he starts",
    "answerDetails": "Then Laura raises her hand. “I think,” she begins to say."
  },
  {
    "id": 682,
    "question": "marido",
    "questionDetails": "Mi marido me regaló un precioso ramo de rosas.",
    "answer": "husband",
    "answerDetails": "My husband gave me a lovely bouquet of roses."
  },
  {
    "id": 683,
    "question": "capaz",
    "questionDetails": "Parecía entusiasta y capaz.",
    "answer": "capable",
    "answerDetails": "She looked enthusiastic and capable."
  },
  {
    "id": 684,
    "question": "perfectamente",
    "questionDetails": "Harry compró una billetera europea para que los billetes de euro encajaran perfectamente en Ella.",
    "answer": "neatly",
    "answerDetails": "Harry bought a European wallet so that the euro bills would fit neatly into it."
  },
  {
    "id": 685,
    "question": "tenías",
    "questionDetails": "Tú tenías mi anillo.",
    "answer": "had",
    "answerDetails": "You had my ring."
  },
  {
    "id": 686,
    "question": "gustan",
    "answer": "Like"
  },
  {
    "id": 687,
    "question": "verlo",
    "questionDetails": "¿Vas a ir al juego?-No, voy a verlo en la Televisión.",
    "answer": "watch it",
    "answerDetails": "Are you going to the game?-No, I’m going to watch it on television."
  },
  {
    "id": 688,
    "question": "significa",
    "questionDetails": "¿Ves esta palabra? Significa “comida” en alemán.",
    "answer": "it means",
    "answerDetails": "See this word? It means “food” in German."
  },
  {
    "id": 689,
    "question": "sirve",
    "questionDetails": "Carla es una tenista formidable. Sirve la pelota con tanta fuerza que pocos la pueden devolver.",
    "answer": "she serves, will do",
    "answerDetails": "Carla is a formidable tennis player. She serves the ball so hard that few can return it."
  },
  {
    "id": 690,
    "question": "baja",
    "questionDetails": "El jefe estuvo de baja toda la semana.",
    "answer": "sick leave",
    "answerDetails": "The boss was on sick leave the whole week."
  },
  {
    "id": 691,
    "question": "padres",
    "questionDetails": "Mis padres me dijeron que dejara de ir.",
    "answer": "parents, fathers, dads",
    "answerDetails": "My parents told me to stop going."
  },
  {
    "id": 692,
    "question": "regalo",
    "questionDetails": "El regalo de su madre de una pluma.",
    "answer": "gift, present, giveaway",
    "answerDetails": "His mother’s gift of a pen."
  },
  {
    "id": 693,
    "question": "grandes",
    "questionDetails": "Esos son demasiado grandes.",
    "answer": "large, big, great",
    "answerDetails": "Those are much too large."
  },
  {
    "id": 694,
    "question": "empezó",
    "questionDetails": "Empezó a trabajar a las 8 am hoy.",
    "answer": "she started, she began",
    "answerDetails": "She started working at 8 A.M. today."
  },
  {
    "id": 695,
    "question": "ibas",
    "questionDetails": "Pensé que nunca ibas a.",
    "answer": "were, IBA",
    "answerDetails": "I thought you were never."
  },
  {
    "id": 696,
    "question": "suficiente",
    "questionDetails": "Usted no es lo suficientemente grande para el baloncesto.",
    "answer": "enough, sufficient",
    "answerDetails": "You’re not big enough for basketball."
  },
  {
    "id": 697,
    "question": "llegado",
    "questionDetails": "Ese momento ha llegado.",
    "answer": "arrived, come, reached",
    "answerDetails": "That moment has now arrived."
  },
  {
    "id": 698,
    "question": "juego",
    "questionDetails": "Cada hogar necesita un juego de herramientas.",
    "answer": "set, gaming, stake",
    "answerDetails": "Every home needs a set of tools."
  },
  {
    "id": 699,
    "question": "dejé",
    "questionDetails": "Te dejé un poco de dinero.",
    "answer": "left, stopped, quit",
    "answerDetails": "I left you a few bucks."
  },
  {
    "id": 700,
    "question": "fondo",
    "questionDetails": "Fondos mpl.",
    "answer": "fund, bottom",
    "answerDetails": "Funds."
  }
]